was I was going to write every morning.
I'd read a whole bunch of books
on how to be a writer, and a lot
of those books said it was really
important to write every day. So
kind of, like, what I was going to do
was I was going to write every morning.
And the result of this
was, like, after a month,
I'd got 20,000 words of something,
which is about project management,
didn't have the title that it has
now. But kind of, I've written
something. And I had no idea what,
to do with it. I had absolutely no
idea what to do with it. And kind
of part of the reason for that, I
think, is that I had this kind of
naive Hollywood view of a cliched
Hollywood view of what it's like to
be a writer. And what happens when
you're a writer is that
you
sit down at a desk
and you type furiously
and in the movies what happens is
like, you know, there's a montage
happen's behind you and the seasons
change. And in the movies it's an
actual typewriter and there's a real
manuscript and the manuscript gets
bigger and bigger and bigger until
you've got a full manuscript and the
book is finished and I imagined that
if I did put in the kind of writing
a thousand words a day that's what
would happen but that didn't happen
at all what happened was I ended up
with 20,000 words and I had no idea
what to do with it and so what I
did as a response to that and that's
kind of what this is
what this card is sulk
is I sulked for six years. I sulked
for six years. I didn't essentially
touch this book for six years because
I had no idea what to do with it.
And that is a bad thing, I think,
because I think like if I hadn't
sulked, if I'd have carried on and
persevered, I could have been through
that book and maybe on my next book
or maybe on my third book by now.
Right?